export const Questions = [
  {
    prompt: "What are the major languages spoken in Andhra Pradesh?",
    optionA: "Odia and Telugu",
    optionB: "Telugu and Urdu",
    optionC: "Telugu and Kannada",
    optionD: "All of the above languages",
    answer: "optionB",
  },
  {
    prompt: "Which of the following is the capital of Arunachal Pradesh?",
    optionA: "Itanagar",
    optionB: "Dispur",
    optionC: "Imphal",
    optionD: "Panaji",
    answer: "optionA",
  },
  {
    prompt: "What is the state flower of Haryana?",
    optionA: "Lotus",
    optionB: "Rhododendron",
    optionC: "Golden Shower",
    optionD: "Not declared",
    answer: "optionA",
  },
  {
    prompt: "Which of the following states is not located in the North?",
    optionA: "Jharkhand",
    optionB: "Jammu and Kashmir",
    optionC: " Himachal Pradesh",
    optionD: "Haryana",
    answer: "optionA",
  },
  {
    prompt: "Which is the largest coffee-producing state of India?",
    optionA: "Kerala",
    optionB: "Tamil Nadu",
    optionC: "Karnataka",
    optionD: "Arunachal Pradesh",
    answer: "optionC",
  },
  {
    prompt: "Which state has the largest area?",
    optionA: "Maharashtra",
    optionB: "Madhya Pradesh",
    optionC: "Uttar Pradesh",
    optionD: "Rajasthan",
    answer: "optionD",
  },
  {
    prompt: "Dandia' is a popular dance of",
    optionA: "Punjab",
    optionB: "Gujarat",
    optionC: "Tamil Nadu",
    optionD: "Maharashtra",
    answer: "optionB",
  },
  {
    prompt: "The book of Parsis is",
    optionA: "Torah",
    optionB: "Bible",
    optionC: "Zend Avesta",
    optionD: "Gita",
    answer: "optionC",
  },
  {
    prompt: "'Kathakali' is a folk dance prevalent in which state?",
    optionA: "Karnataka",
    optionB: "Orissa",
    optionC: "Kerala",
    optionD: "Manipur",
    answer: "optionC",
  },
  {
    prompt: "Which state has the largest population?",
    optionA: "Uttar Pradesh",
    optionB: "Maharastra",
    optionC: "Bihar",
    optionD: "Andra Pradesh",
    answer: "optionA",
  },
];
